Guide to the Adriana Miller papers, 1950-2010 MS2005
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Audio and visual materials, 1961-2002; MS2005 Series 3
  - Videocassettes: (cymbal) 1.Workshop, Clinton, MD 2.Interview Adriana @ Schmitt 3. Larry Denny, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Item 30)
  - Videocassettes: Zorba The Greek, 1964; Series 3 (Box 10, Item 31)
- Phonographs, 1961-1984; MS2005 Series 4
  This series contains phonographs used by Adriana Miller for her performances and at her school. The dates include 1961-1984.
  - Abou Harba et son ensemble, 1973; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 1)
  - Alla-Turca The Turkish Way Belly Dance with Orzel Turkbas, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 2)
  - An Evening in Beirut, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 3)
  - An Hour with N. Gounaris, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 4)
  - And All Ports East by Gus Vali and his Orchestra, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 5)
  - "Arabesque" Traditional and Folk Dances of the Near East, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 6)
  - Armenian Fun Times Featuring: Mike and Buddy Sarkissian, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 7)
  - Armenian Strings with Leo Derderian, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 8)
  - The Art of Belly Dancing: George Abdo and his "Flames of Araby" Orchestra, 1973; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 9)
  - Artistic Moods for Dance: Fred Elias Ensemble with John Tatassopoulos, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 10)
  - Artistic Moods for Dance Volume 11: The Fred Elias Ensemble, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 11)
  - Artistic Moods for Dance Volume III: The Fred Elias Ensemble with John Tatassopoulos, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 12)
  - Belly Dance A Gift from Cairo! Arranged and Prepared by Youssef Kassab and Hamouda Ali, 1980; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 13)
  - Belly Dance au Go-Go Music of the Middle East: Artie Barsamian and his Orchestra, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 14)
  - Belly Dance Music: The "Flames of Araby" Orchestra Vocals by George Abdo, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 15)
  - Belly Dance Nights Volume 1: Layale Bourg El Haman, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 16)
  - Belly Dance! Spectacular Rhythms from the Middle East, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 17)
  - Belly Dance: The Music of Mohamed Abdel Wahab Volume 1, 1976; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 18)
  - Belly Dancing for Everyone: Chris Kalogerson and The Ensemble Sharqi, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 19)
  - Belly Dancing with George Abdo, 1976; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 20)
  - The Best of Stavros Tzouanakos, 1973; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 21)
  - The Big 30 from Greece: Manolis Hiotis and Mary Linda, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 22)
  - Bouzouki My Love A Selection of Twelve Instrumental Greek Popular Tunes Volume II, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 23)
  - Bring on the Bouzoukee! The Exotic Songs and Dances of Greece Today, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 24)
  - Caravan Melodies of the Middle East, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 25)
  - Cljda Pekkcun, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 26)
  - Concerto for Bouzoukee Volume II, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 27)
  - Coronet Music of the Middle East: Hassan the Assassin, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 28)
  - Dahlena's Middle Eastern Music for Belly Dancing Vol. 2, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 29)
  - Dance Illusion Raja, 1984; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 30)
  - "Dance of the Hareem", 1965; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 31)
  - Dances for Festive Nights, undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 32)
  - Disco East by Greek Salad with Gus Kamaras, 1979; Series 5 (Box 5, Item 33)
  - Egyptian Nights Favorite Melodies from the Middle East for Belly Dancing, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 1)
  - "El Layalli El Hilwa" Exotic Dance Music of the Near East, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 2)
  - Encore! Trio Bel Canto, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 3)
  - Ethnic Dances of Greece Authentic Hellenic Music in Hi-Fi, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 4)
  - The Feenjon Goes Greek America's Most Exciting Near East Group, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 5)
  - Flame of Araby Music of the Middle East Kahraman in Oriental Songs, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 6)
  - Folk Songs of Greece, 1961; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 6)
  - Greece: Arranged and Conducted by Manos Hadjidakis, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 7)
  - Greece: Dimitri and his Ensemble, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 8)
  - Greece is...Popular and Folk Dances, 1975; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 9)
  - Greek Dance-Along George Straits Orchestra, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 10)
  - The Greeks Had a Song for It: Gus Vali and his authentic Greek Orchestra, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 11)
  - Greek Hit Parade of Songs: Trio Bel Canto, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 12)
  - Greek Town, USA A Salute to New York's Bouloukee Casbahs, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 13)
  - H Xapa Toy Metanaeth, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 14)
  - Hrach Yacoubian Plays Modern Greek Horas, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 15)
  - Jalaleddin presents Belly Dance Music, 1976; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 16)
  - Jalaleddin presents Bellydance Music Volume Two, 1977; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 17)
  - Jalaleddin Takesh: Habibi dances Beladi Ya Beladi, 1979; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 18)
  - Jimmy Sings Ali Baba, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 19)
  - Join Us! Dance: The Dabka, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 20)
  - The Joy of Belly Dancing, 1975; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 21)
  - Laurice Peters Sings, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 22)
  - Let's Dance the Syrtaki, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 23)
  - Lyra, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 24)
  - Middle East Music Moods of the Casbah: Soubhi Kochak and Hakki Obadia Ensemble, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 25)
  - Monitor Presents "The King of Belly Dance Music" George Abdo and his "Flames of Araby" Orchestra, 1979; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 26)
  - Monitor Presents The Now Sounds of the Middle East featuring George Mgrdichian, Our and his Ensemble, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 27)
  - More of the Fabulous Trio Bel Canto, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 28)
  - Music for an Oriental Dance Volume I, 1973; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 29)
  - Music of the Fellahin, undated; Series 5 (Box 6, Item 30)
  - Music of the Ouled Naii, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 1)
  - Music of the Qaria, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 2)
  - My Songs: Nikos Gounaris, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 3)
  - Mystical Temptations, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 4)
  - Nadira Belly Dances for Youssef Kassab, 1974; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 5)
  - Nick Gounaris and the Trio Belcanto, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 6)
  - Nick Gounaris' Greece, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 7)
  - Oriental Delight Hank Mardigan Sextet featuring George Mgrdichian on the Oud, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 8)
  - Picture Yourself Belly Dancing: The Topkapi Instrumental Ensemble, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 9)
  - Port Said Music of the Middle East Mohammed El-Bakkar and his Oriental Ensemble, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 10)
  - Rare Gems from the Orient: A Collection of Popular Egyptian Dances, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 11)
  - Recorded Live at a Greek Party: The Hellenes - All-Star Greek Musicians and Singers, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 12)
  - Reflections of the Near East featuring Maha, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 13)
  - Rena Dalia Queen of Song featuring John Tatassopoulos and his Compositions, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 14)
  - Rhythms and Dances from Syria Belly Dance!: Damascus Musical Group conducted by Selim Sarwat, 1977; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 15)
  - Sing and Dace with the Trio Bel Canto, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 16)
  - Soiree Orientale, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 17)
  - Songs by Jim Apostolou, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 18)
  - Sono Cairo, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 19)
  - Soul of the East, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 20)
  - Soutelfan, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 21)
  - Strictly Belly Dancing presented by Eddie "The Sheik" Kochak, 1973; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 22)
  - Strictly Belly Dancing the 1st Volume Presented by Eddie "The Sheik" Kochak with Hakki Obadia, 1977; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 23)
  - Strictly Belly Dancing Volume 2 Eddie "The Sheik" Kochak, 1975; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 24)
  - Strictly Belly Dancing the 2nd Volume Eddie "The Sheik" Kochak with Hakki Obadia featuring Joseph Kassab, 1977; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 25)
  - Strictly Belly Dancing Vol. 3 Eddie "The Sheik" Kochak, 1976; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 26)
  - Strictly Belly Dancing Vol. 4 Eddie "The Sheik" Kochak, 1976; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 27)
  - Strictly Belly Dancing the 5th Volume Eddie "The Sheik" Kochak with Hakki Obadia, 1977; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 28)
  - Strictly Belly Dancing the 6th Volume Eddie "The Sheik" Kochak with Hakki Obadia, 1979; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 29)
  - "Trio Kris" Sing with Bouzouki, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 30)
  - Tsiftetelia No 2, 1975; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 31)
  - Voyages Autour du Monde, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 32)
  - Warda, 1978; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 33)
  - Ya Habib! Exciting New Sounds of the Middle East with Eddie "Sheik" Kochak and Hakki Obadia and their Amer-abic Orchestra, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 34)
  - Foreign Title with a Picture of 2 Men on the Front, undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 1)
  - Foreign Title with a Woman Dancing on the Front, undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 2)
  - Foreign Title with a Gold Coin Necklace on the Front, undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 3)
  - Album with Various Records, undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 4)
  - Album with Various Records, undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 5)